<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>QuantCode: The Toolkit for Engineering-Driven Traders.</title>
    <link>https://quantcodedenny.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on QuantCode: The Toolkit for Engineering-Driven Traders.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:09:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://quantcodedenny.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>https://quantcodedenny.com/posts/challenge-in-vibe-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quantcodedenny.com/posts/challenge-in-vibe-coding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;technical-challenges&#34;&gt;Technical challenges&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multiple versions: functions may be undefined or unsupported across versions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understanding conventions: e.g., Hugo generates files into the `docs` folder, not `content`.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lack of defensive coding: errors propagate, making debugging harder.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ox-hugo 0.12.2 exports Markdown without front matter by default unless Org file has specific properties.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;LLM behavior: when facing impossible tasks, it often loops endlessly instead of admitting &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;gaps-and-blind-spots&#34;&gt;Gaps &amp;amp; blind spots&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Works well for individual files, but not full project structures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[#A] You don’t know what you don’t know—and the LLM may not tell you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Component limitations arise from business, capability, or incompatibilities:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Business: e.g., Twitter free API only allows pulling 100 posts/day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Capability: e.g., Emacs plugin (ox-hugo) only supports Markdown blocks in Org files.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Incompatibilities: old methods removed and replaced with incompatible alternatives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;expert-mindset-for-vibe-coding&#34;&gt;Expert mindset for vibe coding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Embrace imperfection: treat the LLM as a co-pilot, not a guarantee.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Iterate fast: copy errors to the LLM and ask for fixes immediately—speed &amp;gt; perfect understanding.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Meta-awareness: question assumptions about project structure, plugin limitations, or API behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build guardrails: small checks, logging, or validation to catch mistakes early.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Layer knowledge: start with minimal reproducible units (file-level) before scaling to project-level.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Document gaps: track behaviors, limitations, and “unknown unknowns” to avoid repeating mistakes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tool orchestration: combine LLM, Emacs, Hugo, and API limitations strategically—know which tool to push and where manual intervention is cheaper.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;caveats-workflow-tips&#34;&gt;Caveats / Workflow tips&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Don’t overanalyze error messages; capture them and ask the LLM to propose fixes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Recognize impossible tasks early—stop LLM loops.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Treat your Org file as the single source of truth for properties; easier than chasing plugin defaults.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use LLM for stock sentiment</title>
      <link>https://quantcodedenny.com/posts/llm-stock-sentiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quantcodedenny.com/posts/llm-stock-sentiment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This tool empowers engineers to automate stock sentiment analysis with&#xA;precision and speed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It combines two core capabilities: parsing recent&#xA;news headlines to extract market sentiment and insights, and parsing&#xA;SEC filings to surface key financial and risk information. Both&#xA;streams are fed into a configurable LLM pipeline, allowing you to run&#xA;fast local tests with lightweight models or perform high-accuracy&#xA;production analysis. Designed for modularity and reuse, it integrates&#xA;seamlessly into your workflows—turning raw data into actionable&#xA;insights without manual reading.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
